[
    {
        "qid": 638821,
        "question": "Patient is a 29 year old female.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient feels their heart is beating fast (racing), irregularly (missing a beat), or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has recently taken decongestants or other substances that may have stimulant effects.",
        "option1": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option2": "Boerhaave",
        "option3": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option4": "Epiglottitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "49%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 171415,
        "question": "Patient is a 8 year old female.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, the side of the chest (right), and the upper chest.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient feels out of breath with minimal physical effort.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has traveled to North America in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Scombroid food poisoning",
        "option4": "Myocarditis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "70%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1083084,
        "question": "Patient is a 32 year old male.<br>- The patient has been in contact with a person with similar symptoms in the past 2 weeks.<br>- The patient has been coughing up blood.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, thyroid cartilage, and pharynx.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is immunosuppressed.",
        "option1": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option2": "Influenza",
        "option3": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option4": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "76%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 326448,
        "question": "Patient is a 44 year old male.<br>- The patient feels anxious.<br>- The patient regularly drinks coffee or tea.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a cramp.<br>- The patient feels pain in their left temple.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient consumes energy drinks regularly.<br>- The patient regularly takes stimulant drugs.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels that their heart is beating fast, irregularly, or they feel palpitations.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Panic attack",
        "option2": "HIV (initial infection)",
        "option3": "Acute pulmonary edema",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "62%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 1045460,
        "question": "Patient is a 34 year old female.<br>- The patient has been coughing up blood.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has recently had a loss of appetite or gets full more quickly than usual.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option4": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "67%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 103892,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the upper chest.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a cough that produces colored or more abundant sputum than usual.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has chronic obstructive pulmonary disease (COPD).<br>- The patient has a cough.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's symptoms are more prominent at night.",
        "option1": "Localized edema",
        "option2": "Pulmonary embolism",
        "option3": "Pancreatic neoplasm",
        "option4": "Bronchitis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "58%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 779274,
        "question": "Patient is a 3 year old male.<br>- The patient has recently had a viral infection.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is characterized as a knife stroke.<br>- The patient feels pain in the lower chest, side of the chest (left), upper chest, right breast, and left breast.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient has noticed new fatigue, generalized and vague discomfort, diffuse (widespread) muscle aches, or a change in their general well-being related to their consultation today.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Pneumonia",
        "option2": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "option3": "Myocarditis",
        "option4": "Guillain-Barr√© syndrome",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 482974,
        "question": "Patient is a 49 year old female.<br>- The patient has been coughing up blood.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the posterior chest wall on the right side.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 1 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is experiencing shortness of breath or difficulty breathing in a significant way.<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient constantly feels fatigued or has non-restful sleep.<br>- The patient has had an involuntary weight loss over the last 3 months.<br>- The patient is a former smoker.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has family members who have had lung cancer.",
        "option1": "Influenza",
        "option2": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option3": "Myasthenia gravis",
        "option4": "Sarcoidosis",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "47%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 17005,
        "question": "Patient is a 23 year old male.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive, tugging, and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in their lower chest.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest and upper chest.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 0 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient is significantly overweight compared to people of the same height as them.<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.<br>- The patient's symptoms are worse when lying down and alleviated while sitting up.",
        "option1": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option2": "Acute dystonic reactions",
        "option3": "Pneumonia",
        "option4": "Localized edema",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 2,
        "ai_confidence": "78%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1049152,
        "question": "Patient is a 36 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right cheek, left cheek, and left temple.<br>- The patient's pain intensity is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has diffuse (widespread) muscle pain.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient is exposed to secondhand cigarette smoke on a daily basis.",
        "option1": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "option2": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "option3": "Viral pharyngitis",
        "option4": "Anaphylaxis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "60%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 581455,
        "question": "Patient is a 70 year old female.<br>- The patient has a poor diet.<br>- The patient has had a diagnosis of anemia.<br>- The patient does not feel pain anywhere.<br>- The patient feels slightly dizzy or lightheaded.<br>- The patient feels lightheaded and dizzy or feels like they are about to faint.<br>- The patient feels so tired that they are unable to do their usual activities or are stuck in bed all day long.<br>- The patient has chronic kidney failure.<br>- The patient is taking new oral anticoagulants (NOACs).<br>- The patient's skin is much paler than usual.<br>- The patient thinks they are pregnant or are currently pregnant.<br>- The patient has traveled to North Africa in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient's BMI is less than 18.5, or they are underweight.",
        "option1": "Sarcoidosis",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Guillain-Barr√© syndrome",
        "option4": "Inguinal hernia",
        "correct_option": 4,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "68%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 1057572,
        "question": "Patient is a 50 year old female.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tugging and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the belly and epigastric regions.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain radiates to the lower chest and upper chest.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 5 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a hiatal hernia.<br>- The patient has asthma or has had to use a bronchodilator in the past.<br>- The patient has a burning sensation that starts in their stomach, goes up into their throat, and can be associated with a bitter taste in their mouth.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has symptoms that get worse after eating.",
        "option1": "Cluster headache",
        "option2": "Gastroesophageal reflux disease (GERD)",
        "option3": "Allergic sinusitis",
        "option4": "Systemic lupus erythematosus (SLE)",
        "correct_option": 2,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "42%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    },
    {
        "qid": 800573,
        "question": "Patient is a 35 year old female.<br>- The patient attends or works in a daycare.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive.<br>- The patient feels pain in the thyroid cartilage, palate, pharynx, and under the jaw.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 2 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The patient's pain is located with a precision of 6 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Myasthenia gravis",
        "option2": "Anemia",
        "option3": "Pericarditis",
        "option4": "Acute laryngitis",
        "correct_option": 3,
        "ai_prediction": 3,
        "ai_confidence": "48%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 850052,
        "question": "Patient is a 62 year old male.<br>- The patient lives with 4 or more people.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is sensitive and burning.<br>- The patient feels pain in the right tonsil, left tonsil, pharynx, and trachea.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is precisely located at a level of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient smokes cigarettes.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.<br>- The patient has noticed that the tone of their voice has become deeper, softer, or hoarse.",
        "option1": "Bronchospasm / acute asthma exacerbation",
        "option2": "Acute laryngitis",
        "option3": "Pulmonary neoplasm",
        "option4": "Paroxysmal supraventricular tachycardia (PSVT)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 1,
        "ai_confidence": "93%",
        "ai_is_correct": true
    },
    {
        "qid": 410465,
        "question": "Patient is a 5 year old female.<br>- The patient has had significantly increased sweating.<br>- The patient has pain somewhere, related to their reason for consulting.<br>- The patient's pain is tedious and heavy.<br>- The patient feels pain at the top of the head, forehead, and occiput.<br>- The intensity of the patient's pain is 7 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient's pain does not radiate to another location.<br>- The pain is located with a precision of 3 (on a scale of 0 to 10) for the patient.<br>- The patient's pain appeared at a speed of 4 (on a scale of 0 to 10).<br>- The patient has a fever, either felt or measured with a thermometer.<br>- The patient has a sore throat.<br>- The patient has nasal congestion or a clear runny nose.<br>- The patient has not traveled out of the country in the last 4 weeks.",
        "option1": "Possible NSTEMI / STEMI",
        "option2": "Panic attack",
        "option3": "Pericarditis",
        "option4": "Upper respiratory tract infection (URTI)",
        "correct_option": 1,
        "ai_prediction": 4,
        "ai_confidence": "73%",
        "ai_is_correct": false
    }
]